Conservative Party Archive: Constituency Correspondence CPA CCO 1
Conservative Party Archive
- Constituency files, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9
  - Area N - Scotland, Sep 1951-Aug 1953
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Ross and Cromarty, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/568; 1.0 file
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Western Isles, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/569; 1.0 file
    - Kircudbrightshire and Wigtownshire, Galloway, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/570; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Bridgeton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/571; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Camlachie, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/572; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Cathcart, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/573; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Central, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/574; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Gorbels, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/575; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Govan, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/576; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Hillhead, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/577; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Kelvingrove, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/578; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Maryhill, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/579; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Pollock, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/580; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Scotstoun, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/581; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Shettleston, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/582; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Springburn, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/583; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Tradeston, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/584; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Woodside, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/585; 1.0 file
    - Coatbridge and Airdrie, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/586; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Bothwell, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/587; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Hamilton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/588; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Lanark, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/589/1; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Lanark, By-Election, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/589/2; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Motherwell, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/590; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/591; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Rutherglen, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/592; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Central, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/593; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/594; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Leith, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/595; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/596; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Pentlands, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/597; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/598; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/599; 1.0 file
    - Midlothian and Peebles, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/600; 1.0 file
    - Moray and Nairnshire, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/601; 1.0 file
    - Orkney and Zetland, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/602; 1.0 file
    - Perthshire and Kinross-shire, Kinross and West Perthshire, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/603; 1.0 file
    - Perthshire and Kinross-shire, Perth and East Perthshire, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/604; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire and Greenock, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/605; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire and Paisley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/606; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire, East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/607; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire, West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/608; 1.0 file
    - Roxburgh and Selkirk, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/609; 1.0 file
    - Stirling and Falkirk Burghs, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/610; 1.0 file
    - Stirlingshire and Clackmannan, Clackmannan and East Stirlingshire, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/611; 1.0 file
    - Stirlingshire and Clackmannan, West Stirlingshire, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/612; 1.0 file
    - West Lothian, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/613; 1.0 file
    - [Vacant], Sep 1951-Aug 1953; [CCO 1/9/614]
  - Area O - Northern Ireland, Sep 1951-Aug 1953
    CCO 1/9/615-CCO 1/9/625
    - Northern Ireland, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/615/625; 1.0 file
    - Belfast South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/616; 1.0 file
    - [Vacant], Sep 1951-Aug 1953; [CCO 1/9/617]
    - North Antrim, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/618; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Sep 1953-Feb 1955
  - Area A - London, Sep 1953-Feb 1955
    CCO 1/10/1-CCO 1/10/43
    - Battersea North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/1; 1.0 file
    - Battersea South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/2; 1.0 file
    - Bermondsey, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/3; 1.0 file
    - Bethnal Green, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/4; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Dulwich, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/5; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Peckham, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/6; 1.0 file
    - Chelsea, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/7; 1.0 file
    - Cities of London and Westminster, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/8/1; 1.0 file
    - City of London, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/8/2; 1.0 file
    - City of Westminster, Abbey, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/8/3; 1.0 file
    - City of Westminster, St. George's, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/8/4; 1.0 file
    - Deptford, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/9; 1.0 file
    - Fulham East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/10; 1.0 file
    - Fulham West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/11; 1.0 file
    - Greenwich, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/12; 1.0 file
    - Hackney South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/13; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/14; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/15; 1.0 file
    - Hampstead, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/16; 1.0 file
    - Holborn and St. Pancras South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/17/1; 1.0 file
    - Holborn and St. Pancras South, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/17/2; 1.0 file
    - Holborn and St. Pancras South, By-Election (file B), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/17/3; 1.0 file
    - Holborn and St. Pancras South, By-Election, Organisation Department file, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/17/4; 1.0 file
    - Islington East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/18; 1.0 file
    - Islington North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/19; 1.0 file
    - Islington South West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/20; 1.0 file
    - Kensington North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/21; 1.0 file
    - Kensington South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/22; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Brixton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/23; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Norwood, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/24; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Vauxhall, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/25; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/26; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/27; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/28; 1.0 file
    - Paddington North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/29/1; 1.0 file
    - Paddington North, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/29/2; 1.0 file
    - Paddington North, By-Election (file B), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/29/3; 1.0 file
    - Paddington South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/30; 1.0 file
    - Poplar, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/31; 1.0 file
    - St. Marylebone, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/32; 1.0 file
    - St. Pancras North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/33; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch and Finsbury, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/34/1; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch and Finsbury, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/34/2; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch and Finsbury, By-Election, Organisation Department file, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/34/3; 1.0 file
    - Southwark, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/35; 1.0 file
    - Stepney, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/36; 1.0 file
    - Stoke Newington and Hackney North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/37; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Central, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/38; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth, Clapham, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/39; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth, Putney, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/40; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth, Streatham, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/41; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/42; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/43; 1.0 file
  - Area B - Northern, Sep 1953-Feb 1955
    CCO 1/10/44-CCO 1/10/77
    - Carlisle, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/44; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Penrith, and the Border Division, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/45; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Whitehaven Division, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/46; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Workington, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/47; 1.0 file
    - Darlington, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/48; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/49/50; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/49; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/50; 1.0 file
    - South Shields, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/51; 1.0 file
    - Stockton-on-Tees, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/52; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/53/54; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/53; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/54; 1.0 file
    - The Hartlepools, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/55; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Bishop Aukland, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/56; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Blaydon, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/57; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Chester-le-Street, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/58; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Consett, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/59; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Durham, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/60; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Easington, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/61; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Houghton-le-Spring, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/62; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Jarrow, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/63; 1.0 file
    - Durham, North West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/64; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Sedgefield, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/65; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/66/67; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/66; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/67; 1.0 file
    - Blyth, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/68; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle Central, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/69; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/70; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/71; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/72; 1.0 file
    - Tynemouth, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/73; 1.0 file
    - Wallsend, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/74; 1.0 file
    - Berwick on Tweed, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/75; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle, Hexham, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/76; 1.0 file
    - Northumberland, Morpeth, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/77/1; 1.0 file
    - Northumberland, Morpeth, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/77/2; 1.0 file
    - Northumberland, Morpeth, By-Election, Organisation Department file, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/77/3; 1.0 file
  - Area C - North West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955
    CCO 1/10/78-CCO 1/10/157
    - Altrincham and Sale, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/78; 1.0 file
    - Bebington, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/79; 1.0 file
    - Birkenhead, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/80; 1.0 file
    - Stockport, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/81/82; 1.0 file
    - Stockport North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/81; 1.0 file
    - Stockport South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/82/1; 1.0 file
    - Stockport South, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/82/2; 1.0 file
    - Stockport South, By-Election, Organisation Department file, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/82/3; 1.0 file
    - Wallasey, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/83; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Cheadle, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/84; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, City of Chester, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/85; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Crewe, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/86; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Knutsford, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/87; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Macclesfield, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/88; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Northwich, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/89; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Runcorn, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/90; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Stalybridge and Hyde, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/91; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Wirral, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/92; 1.0 file
    - Accrington, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/93; 1.0 file
    - Ashton-Under-Lyne, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/94; 1.0 file
    - Barrow-in Furness, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/95; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/96/97; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/96; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/97; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/98/99; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/98; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/99; 1.0 file
    - Bolton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/100/101; 1.0 file
    - Bolton East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/100; 1.0 file
    - Bolton West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/101; 1.0 file
    - Bootle, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/102; 1.0 file
    - Burnley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/103; 1.0 file
    - Bury and Radcliffe, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/104; 1.0 file
    - Crosby, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/105/1; 1.0 file
    - Crosby, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/105/2; 1.0 file
    - Crosby, By-Election (file B), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/105/3; 1.0 file
    - Droylsden, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/106; 1.0 file
    - Eccles, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/107; 1.0 file
    - Leigh, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/108; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/109/117; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Edgehill, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/109; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Exchange, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/110; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Garston, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/111; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Kirkdale, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/112; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Scotland, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/113; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Toxteth, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/114; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Walton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/115; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Wavertree, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/116; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool West Derby, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/117/1; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool West Derby, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/117/2; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool West Derby, By-Election (file B), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/117/3; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool West Derby, By-Election, Organisation Department file, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/117/4; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/118/126; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Ardwick, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/118; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Blackley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/119; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Cheetham, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/120; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Clayton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/121; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Exchange, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/122; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Gorton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/123; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Moss Side, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/124; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Withington, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/125; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Wythenshawe, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/126; 1.0 file
    - Nelson and Colne, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/127; 1.0 file
    - Oldham, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/128/129; 1.0 file
    - Oldham East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/128; 1.0 file
    - Oldham West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/129; 1.0 file
    - Preston, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/130/131; 1.0 file
    - Preston North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/130; 1.0 file
    - Preston South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/131; 1.0 file
    - Rochdale, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/132; 1.0 file
    - Rossendale, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/133; 1.0 file
    - St. Helen's, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/134; 1.0 file
    - Salford, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/135/136; 1.0 file
    - Salford East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/135; 1.0 file
    - Salford West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/136; 1.0 file
    - Southport, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/137; 1.0 file
    - Stretford, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/138; 1.0 file
    - Warrington, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/139; 1.0 file
    - Wigan, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/140; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Chorley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/141; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Clithero, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/142; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Darwen, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/143; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Farnworth, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/144; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Heywood and Royton (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/145/1; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Heywood and Royton (file B), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/145/2; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Huyton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/146; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ince, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/147; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Lancaster, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/148; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Middleton and Prestwich, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/149; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Morecombe and Lonsdale, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/150; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Newton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/151; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, North Fylde, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/152; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ormskirk, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/153/1; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ormskirk- By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/153/2; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ormskirk- By-Election (file B), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/153/3; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, South Fylde, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/154; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Westhoughton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/155; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Widnes, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/156; 1.0 file
    - Westmorland, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/157; 1.0 file
  - Area D - Yorkshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955
    CCO 1/10/158-CCO 1/10/213
    - Barnsley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/158/1; 1.0 file
    - Mid-Yorkshire Federation, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/158/2; 1.0 file
    - Bately and Morley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/159; 1.0 file
    - Bradford, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/160/163; 1.0 file
    - Bradford Central, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/160; 1.0 file
    - Bradford East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/161; 1.0 file
    - Bradford North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/162; 1.0 file
    - Bradford South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/163; 1.0 file
    - Brighouse and Spenborough, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/164; 1.0 file
    - Dewsbury, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/165; 1.0 file
    - Doncaster, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/166; 1.0 file
    - Halifax, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/167; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/168/169; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/168; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/169; 1.0 file
    - Keighley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/170; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/171/174; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Central, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/171; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/172; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Haltemprice, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/173/1; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Haltemprice, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/173/2; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Haltemprice, By-Election (file B), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/173/3; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Haltemprice, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/173/4; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Haltemprice - Speakers' Department file, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/173/5; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/174; 1.0 file
    - Leeds, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/175/181; 1.0 file
    - Leeds Central, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/175; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/176; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/177; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/178; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/179; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/180; 1.0 file
    - Leeds West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/181; 1.0 file
    - Pontefract, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/182; 1.0 file
    - Pudsey, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/183; 1.0 file
    - Rotherham, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/184; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/185/191; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Attercliffe, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/185; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Brightside, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/186; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Hallam, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/187; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Healey, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/188; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Hillsborough, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/189; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Neepsend, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/190; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield Park, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/191; 1.0 file
    - Wakefield, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/192/1; 1.0 file
    - Wakefield, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/192/2; 1.0 file
    - Wakefield, By-Election (file B), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/192/3; 1.0 file
    - Wakefield, By-Election, Organisation Department file, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/192/4; 1.0 file
    - York, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/193; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Barkston Ash, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/194; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Beverley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/195; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Bridlington, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/196; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Cleveland, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/197; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Colne Valley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/198; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Dearne Valley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/199; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Don Valley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/200; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Goole, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/201; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Harrogate, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/202/1; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Harrogate, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/202/2; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Harrogate, By-Election (file B), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/202/3; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Harrogate, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/202/4; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Hemsworth, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/203; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Normanton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/204; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Penistone, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/205; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/206; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Rippon, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/207; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Rother Valley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/208; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Scarborough and Whitby, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/209; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Shipley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/210; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Skipton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/211; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Sowerby, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/212; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Thirsk and Malton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/213; 1.0 file
  - Area E - East Midlands, Sep 1953-Feb 1955
    CCO 1/10/214-CCO 1/10/255
    - Chesterfield, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/214; 1.0 file
    - Derby, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/215/216; 1.0 file
    - Derby North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/215; 1.0 file
    - Derby South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/216; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, Belper, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/217; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, Bolsover, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/218; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, High Peak, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/219; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, Ilkeston, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/220; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, North East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/221; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, South East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/222; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/223; 1.0 file
    - Leicester, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/224/227; 1.0 file
    - Leicester North East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/224; 1.0 file
    - Leicester North West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/225; 1.0 file
    - Leicester South East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/226; 1.0 file
    - Leicester South West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/227; 1.0 file
    - Leicestershire, Bosworth, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/228; 1.0 file
    - Leicestershire, Harborough, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/229; 1.0 file
    - Leicestershire, Loughborough, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/230; 1.0 file